comparing and rating Indian dupes of
viral beauty products starting with this
viral milk jelly cheek and lip stain
which has been duped by PR Beauty in
terms of application feel and even
efficacy these two are identical both of
these are very long lasting and even
water resistant I would rate this dup
for 10 on 10 next comparing Haley
Bieber's Road lip tint with Cy sanon's
hyphen lip balms the road ones
definitely more moisturizing but in
terms of finish they are so similar I
just wish the hyphen one wasn't this
overly sweet to taste I'm rating this an
8 on 10 I've tried this entire range
from Soul the Janeiro and it smells
incredible but the plum body love and
vanilla caramel range smells identical
and probably even lasts a lot longer I
find the duper better value for money
and I'm going to rate it an 11 on 10
lastly comparing these iconic Charlotte
Tilbury lipsticks with these ones by
Revlon you really cannot tell the shades
apart but I feel the Charlotte ones feel
a little bit more moisturizing so I'm
going to rate the dup a 9 on 10 do like
and subscribe for more such videos and
I'll see you